[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "NNPS", ":", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Should there be a criteria -- you know, should we elect a politician who's 89?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I think we need to recognize that we're living longer as Americans -- as people in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "So do we have to stop being less politically correct and just call it as we see it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, I think it goes to performance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "I think this is about (INAUDIBLE), right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "But we also get to select.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "When do we take somebody's driver's license away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "POS", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "When they can't drive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Is it OK to call people out for being overweight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Big Macs"]}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBG", "JJR", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 219, "question": "No, but you're asking, is it OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "The people eating more Big Macs isn't necessarily driving us to --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Why don't you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Well, the --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "First of all, do you have any promise whatsoever that this SEAL came out and told this story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, we're getting into dangerous stuff when we start giving away secrets and things like that, but I think what it goes to is these guys aren't treated well when they come home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stan"]}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "So, can we blame somebody who is brought up in this generation -- can we expect anybody anywhere in any capacity to keep anything private anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "I got to be honest with you, I think Stan nailed this one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "He's going to get nothing from it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "ALE: This man doesn't get a pension.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Does a woman in the public eye have an obligation to make a statement to her fans, to young women who follower, say this is not okay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "JJR", ",", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Did you see, he was the only one not standing for Ocean when he got his award?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Oh yeah, but that's the problem -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "So, we have a problem with Rihanna, what she's doing, and not with what Bobby Brown did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Chris brown.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rihanna"], "PERSON": ["Bobby Brown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "How much have you heard about Demi Moore lately?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Yes, not anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Demi Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "What's the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I don't think she's having a great time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Grammys"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "I mean, Lindsay Lohan, would we be talking about her if not for her hijinx?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "When I was watching the Grammys last night, I was looking around at the guys saying who is her next target, because that's just how you view her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lindsay Lohan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Am I wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "But she does -- when you say that, it makes her sound like a man eater.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "How old is she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "She's like 23.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Are we not getting it, nipping it in the bud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "No, when I was a kid, my parents wouldn't even let us have water guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "I feel like we're probably, if I had to guess, not going to end up getting background checks done, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "I don't even know about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Military people are people's heroes because they hold guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "In large part their job -- we talked about the hero before that killed Osama bin Laden.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Do they even matter anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "You can't -- but what can we do more now, Stan, across the board, early on, to start to detect some of the mental problems in this country, the mental -- horrible health situation in the country so we don't get to this point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "Well, there's a big stigma on mental health, first of all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "If they had a technology now that early on could test children for various mental disorders, would you say that's invasive or OK to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "Oh my God, I'm investing in that company.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "When are we going to start talking about the awesome?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "All right guys, we got to take a break here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "Are these people just wasting their time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "Of course, they can get it back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno", "Casey Anthony", "Joe Paterno"]}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "Yeah, once people make their decision, if anything, Abby, doesn't it backfire on them because now you look at them and go, they're just cashing in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "For the most part, but I think Joe Paterno is different than like a Casey Anthony because Joe Paterno has so much good will to stand on.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Abby"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gary"]}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "Or am I just being naive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "That's what Gary was talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 882, "question": "Doesn't he look like a cruise guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 883, "answer": "I just went on one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 919, "question": "ALIE: Have you ever been on a cruise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 920, "answer": "Three times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Samsung"]}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 936, "question": "Has Samsung now taken the lead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 937, "answer": "Not Samsung.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Samsung"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 965, "question": "Guys, does everybody have a problem when you're out to dinner and everybody's going like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 966, "answer": "No, it's fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]